Episode 9
My Childhood Friend Becomes My Apprentice?
I Want to End This Love Game
What should we get for lunch?
Meeting
In
Progress
Student Council Room
m 1349.001 411.999 l 1349.001 462 l 1497.999 462 l 1497.999 411.999
m 0 0 l 0 107.001 l 42.999 107.001 l 42.999 0
Meeting
In
Progress
m 0 9 l 6 396.999 l 201.999 393.999 l 195 0
Sakura-san.
Please teach me how to
play the Love Game again.
What happened this time?
We tried that thing yesterday.
The prod thing.
But I used a bit too much force, and...
He was like, "What is this,
Fist of the N Star?"
Why'd you have to stab him?
I mean, his body shape's
nothing like when we were kids,
and seeing him up close, well...
I-I get the feeling!
After he's grown way taller than her
I don't think I can pull it off.
I can't get us beyond
just childhood friends.
I was hoping Kakeru would notice me,
even just a little, but...
It's too soon to give up!
And you call yourself
the Blood-Soaked Lily?
Th-That's not a nickname
I'm particularly proud of.
I'll teach you some more.
We'll show him!
That's convincing coming from people
who went from childhood
friends to being in love.
Huh?
We aren't exactly in love with each other.
Wha?
That's clearly not true.
You're mutually in love.
I-It's true that I have... er...
Mumble,
mumble
On the other hand,
I don't know how he feels.
Which is why I'm playing the game
to try to get him to say I'm cute.
But he just won't...
Oh, please don't tell Yukiya about this.
Thank you, Sakura-san.
I'm counting on you.
Yup! Let's make it happen!
Okay, thank you in advance, master!
M-Maybe don't call me master.
First, you play Kakeru.
I'll try retaliating.
Wait, wait, wait...
Man, it's hot.
What's wrong, Kazane?
You're beet red.
Did I happen to get your heart racing?
Come on, Senpai.
You can't just sit there blushing.
In these situations...
You're the one stricken by me.
Debauchery!
In that moment, her life
flashed before her eyes.
Miku-chan.
Grandma's calling my name.
I'm sorry!
Sakura-san, what's going through your
mind when you do this kind of thing?
What's going th-th-through my mind?
I'm just hoping to tease Yukiya for
being overwhelmed by my cuteness.
I see...
So you like seeing Asagi-kun
flustered and in a panic.
N-No!
I mean, well,
when he tries to retaliate even
though he doesn't have it in him,
that's kind of cute.
But considering that your act was
more like Asagi-kun than Kakeru,
and considering that was the first
thing that came to your mind...
Sakura-san, is that the kind of
thing that gets you turned on?
Perhaps you have some slightly
masochistic proclivities?
Lewd!
Why won't you give a straight answer?!
It isn't lewd!
Later! See you tomorrow.
'Sup!
Kakeru Chigusa
Kazane's Childhood Friend
Student Council General Admin
A few minutes ago
I gotta be somewhere real quick.
I'll leave my bag here.
Now's my chance.
As soon as Kakeru gets back,
I'm going to do what
Sakura-san did, and...
Hey, Kazane, I'm home.
"I-I'm home"?!
Does he think this is his place?
Our home?
That would make us a married couple!
Hey, I'm home.
I bought some
toilet paper
on the way back.
Hey, I'm home.
I bought some toilet paper
on the way back.
Are you all right?
You look like you have a fever.
No!
Huh? Wh-What's wrong?
Oh, is my belt loose?
We had gym today, so...
Close call.
Oh, right, never mind that.
Kazane.
Huh? What?
Athletic tape?
I got some from the nurse's office.
You sprained your finger when you
jabbed my stomach yesterday, didn't you?
I'm surprised you noticed.
Of course I would.
It's not a big deal. Relax.
You shouldn't underestimate injury.
Hey...
Um...
That's enough.
Thanks.
Sure.
No prob.
Café
Did the student council
president figure it out?
Yeah, I'm sure she'll be fine.
She's doing her best.
I never thought my Love Game experience
would be useful for anyone else.
What a weird feeling.
Yukiya.
Draw me a heart.
What? Why?
Are you embarrassed?
Catching feelings, maybe?
Write "you're lovely."
Even more demands.
Here we go.
Here we go!
Lo
Loser
Look at you, getting so
worked up over omurice.
What a loser.
Yukiya isn't supposed to
be so good at this!
I'm going to make him say I'm cute!
I Want to End This Love Game
Toridenami Bookstore
Such a beautiful mindset.
I should try not to forget it.
Things are going well with Yukiya lately.
I should refine my cuteness
even more to teach him a lesson.
But I can't be cute like someone else.
I have to be special.
Da-ding!
Quiz for the lonely loner
sitting all by his lonesome.
Get it right and you'll get a snack.
What's a cute little squid
that goes well with sumiso?
The firefly squid!
What's the king of squids?
Group Assignment - Group 1
Bigfin reef squids?
They don't really come
across kingly, though.
The humidity's killing my hair. I hate this.
Oh, they're back.
Here you go.
Black Bolt
I can have it?
So what is the answer?
Kanegon says he was no good.
That guy you were talking about?
He's too much of a kid.
He laughs his ass off over dirty jokes.
Cringe. He was hot, though.
Gon's so picky when it comes to guys.
Miku, do you know anyone?
Don't try to rope Miku into this nonsense!
Crap, I reacted by accident!
Oh, right.
Hey, Asagi-kun, you said you like
that Cosmo Connect anime, right?
Urp!
Hm? What?
They made this as part of a
make-up collab with Cosmo Connect.
They did, huh?
I'll put you in full bloom!
“Cosmo Connect”                          Special Moves Compilation
200,000 views              1 month ago            #cosmoconnect
I don't know much about it,
but it's a cute color, so I bought it.
Wanna see?
Oh, th-that's the Aitaso color.
Er, yeah, they did a good job with that.
It represents the character's
traits well. Super-high quality.
I noticed more women have been
playing social media games lately
and there's some cute merch out there.
Seeing it in person warms my heart.
I can tell the creators
poured their soul into it.
You went off!
What, is she your favorite?
So funny!
Akane finally understands
the amusement that is Yukiya.
Yukiya's hilarious.
I just tried it on.
Look.
It's cute, right?
Uh...
My life would be so much easier
if he never struggled to say yes to that.
Yup. It's super cute.
Is it a bit glittery?
Yeah! Can you tell? It has lamé in it.
Pretty!
Yeah, it makes you think of
Aitaso's special attack.
Wow, you're hella studious.
You're doing the group
assignment by yourself?
No, well...
I didn't have any good
comments during class,
so I wanted to at least
write the summary.
Group Assignment - Group 1
So I sent them home.
It's easier working on my own
than in a group anyway.
Wow. You're amazing.
She gave out a compliment.
That never happens.
Oh yeah, wanna add
each other on Instantgram?
Th-This kid's so weird.
He's too stuck up to install the app.
Says it's too trashy.
I could never get him to.
Actually?
So you're one of those
no-social-media guys, huh?
W-Want me to be an in-between
if you want to get in touch with Yukiya?
I'm not about to steal
your hubby, Miku. Relax.
You're so desperate.
I never said anything like that!
Right, Nacchan?
Mochi!
Say what?!
I-I'm gonna go buy a drink.
Miku's adorable when she's like that.
I blew it!
Grandma...
Miku
That's not the kind of
cute I'm going for.
Sakura-san.
There you are.
You scared me!
What is it, Senpai?
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
Last night, I did some searching online
to figure out how
I might get back at Kakeru.
And I discovered
a devastatingly radical game.
Huh? What's that?
This.
I'm told it's called the Pokitto game.
The game where you each bite
one side and eat toward the middle.
Senpai doesn't know the Pokitto game?
No way.
Such a game must not
be allowed to spread.
It may need to be banned.
Huh? Why shouldn't it be allowed?
What do you mean, what?
You do it knowing that your lips
will come close to meeting.
There has to be some
expectation that you will kiss.
The thrill of it becomes tempting
and must be an ulterior motive.
Absolutely despicable!
Now that she mentions it...
Senpai, is it something you want to try?
N-No.
This is far too advanced for me.
My only option is to have
you write a report on it.
It's lewd indeed, but
there's a lot to learn from it.
I may not be able to accomplish it,
but perhaps you, Sakura-san...
No way. Not even for me.
Oh, I'm sorry. I have to be at a meeting.
Senpai!
Sure, the Pokitto game's come to mind
while I was thinking
about the Love Game, but...
But it's a bit too much.
Is it a bit glittery?
I want Yukiya to see me as a girl.
I want him to say it with his own words.
You're super cute.
School Store
m 0 0 l 2.001 362.001 l 1062 363.999 l 1062 0
Next Day
After Class
Miku was acting pretty normal today.
Morning.
m 0 24 l 3.999 162 l 260.001 138 l 255.999 0
This Morning
Even though she was
a bit weird yesterday.
Was that the same as at
the entrance ceremony?
Was she getting jealous?
Does that mean this is finally my chance?
My perfect chance
to make Miku admit defeat?
Yukiya.
Wait up.
Let's walk home together.
Okay.
Wanna go somewhere along the way?
Okay, sure, I guess.
It's an after-school date.
Are you happy?
Not really.
It'll be our second time.
It's not a big deal.
She can try dragging me
to Starparty again,
but I've already done enough
research to buy Wakana a drink!
Onii-chan...
Thanks!
Easy
Okay.
Oh, right.
I downloaded Instantgram.
That app is so trashy.
I get sick just imagining myself using it.
Suou-san asked me yesterday.
What's the matter?
You look stiff.
Don't worry. I'm not...
You never installed
Instantgram when I asked.
Wait, Miku...
See me later. 6PM.
Meet me at the park.
I blew it.
posts              followers         following
Edit Profile
I was going to make
an account just for Miku
and make it an album
just for the two of us.
Normally, that wouldn't have been
more than a minor argument.
That's how it was at
the entrance ceremony.
Was it the way I said it?
Was it bad timing?
No...
I have a feeling that isn't all.
Wow. You actually showed up.
Why wouldn't I?
She hasn't changed.
It's wrinkled.
That doesn't happen.
What's wrong?
Was it something I did?
I'm sorry if it's
something I didn't notice.
No.
You didn't do anything.
Not you.
I'm challenging you with this.
What?
Are you serious?
Out here?
There's no one here.
What's the matter? Too shy?
That's not it.
Isn't this too much for you, too?
What are you thinking?
Do you know the rules?
If you become embarrassed
and let go, you lose.
Kind of like the Love Game, huh?
If I let go, I lose?
What happens if I keep going?
D-Did we...
We touched.
It's your fault for
freaking out and fidgeting.
But someone was...
I touched.
I touched Miku's...
No, this was an accident.
That wasn't a kiss.
But...
What does Miku think about it?
It broke.
Rematch.
Next Time
My Childhood Friend Is Unstoppable
Wakana here.
As you can see, my brother
can be pretty useless,
but he would tuck me back in
when my blanket fell off and stuff.
I would pretend to stay asleep
and not notice that he's actually kind.
Next episode: "My Childhood
Friend Is Unstoppable."